https://bedrumours.co.nz/privacy-policy/

Find a StockistPRIVACY POLICYPRIVACY STATEMENT1. WHAT PERSONAL DATA DO WE COLLECT?When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products, and other updates.We may, where we have a lawful basis for doing so, also collect personal data about you from third parties who provide us with additional publicly available information about you.*We use this information on an anonymous basis and will never use it to identify any particular user. We won’t be able to link this data to any other data that we hold about you and the purpose of collecting this data is to perform analysis and to help us identify people flows around our stores to maximize the efficiency of our store design. 2.WHEN DO WE COLLECT YOUR DATAWhen you purchase products and services from us in store.When you browse our website and we get your IP address. Our website also uses cookies; to find out more about the use of cookies and how you can manage them, please read our Cookie PolicyWhen you subscribe to our Newsletter to receive offers and newsWhen you contact us or we contact you to take part in surveys, competitions or promotionsWhen you contact our customer services team in store, online or over the phoneWhen you engage with us on social media (by mentioning/tagging Bed Rumours or by contacting us directly) 3. HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA AND WHAT ARE OUR LEGAL REASONS FOR DOING SO?3.1 To Make our Products Available for youWe use your personal data to provide you with the information and products that you request or purchase from us (i.e. to complete certain tasks, processes or orders, take payments (where applicable) and deliver your products), and to communicate with you regarding those products that you purchase from us and respond to your questions and comments;We may also use your personal data to measure how satisfied our customers are and provide customer service (or when you ask us questions on social media);We rely on our contractual arrangements with you as the lawful basis on which we collect and process your personal data when you make an order for products. Alternatively, in some cases, we rely on our legitimate interests as a business (for example, to measure customer satisfaction). Where we rely on our legitimate interests, we will always make sure that we balance these interests against your rights.3.2 For Administrative and Internal Business PurposesIs possible we may use your personal data for our internal business purposes, such as improving our site for a better customer experience for you, improving our products and identifying usage trends to bring more of what you like to the store. We may also use your data to monitor the use of our website and ensure that our website is presented in the most effective and relevant manner for you and your device and setting default options for you (such as location);It is in our legitimate interests as a business to use your personal data in this way. For example, we want to ensure our website is customer friendly and works properly and that our products and services are efficient and of high quality. We also want to make it easy for you to interact with us. Where we rely on our legitimate interests, we will always make sure that we balance these interests against your rights.3.3 For security and legal reasonsWe use your personal data to:Ensure the personal and financial information you provide us is accurate;Conduct fraud checks or prevent other illegal activity;Protect our rights or property (or those of others); andFulfill our legal and compliance-related obligations.In some cases we will use your personal data because it’s necessary for us to comply with a legal obligation (such as if we receive a legitimate request from a law enforcement agency). In other cases (such as the detection of fraud) we will rely on our legitimate interests as a business to use your personal data in this way. Where we rely on our legitimate interests, we will always make sure that we balance these interests against your rights.3.4 To personalize your shopping experience and improve our operationsWe use your personal data to:Provide you with marketing material via email;Analyse what you like the most. This may include information on products you have viewed and sections of our page you’ve visited. This allows us to provide a browsing experience which is relevant to what most of our customers are looking for.It is in our legitimate interests as a business to use your data in this way and we do this in order to enhance your shopping experience with us. This allows us to help you find the products and services which you may be looking for and avoids you having to browse through products or services which are not relevant to you.When we send you marketing material via SMS, and email, we will rely on our legitimate interests as a business, always ensuring that your rights are protected.For information on how we use cookies, please see our Cookie Policy. SECTION 2 – CONSENTHow do you get my consent? When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent or provide you with an opportunity to say no.How do I withdraw my consent? If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at rachel@furniturezone.co.nz or mailing us at:Bed Rumours 9 Cessna Place, Mount Maunganui, 3116SECTION 3 – DISCLOSUREWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service. SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICESIn general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies with respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.Links When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.Google analytics: Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked atSECTION 6 – SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.SECTION 7 – COOKIESHere is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not._session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc)._shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits_shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer. cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart._secure_session_id, unique token, sessional storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.PREF, persistent for a very short period, Set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from whereSECTION 8 – AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.SECTION 9 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at  rachel@furniturezone.co.nz or by mail atBed Rumours Privacy Compliance Officer, 9 Cessna Place, Mount Maunganui, 3129
